https://kaitlincorp.com/privacy

Online Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy applies to the collection, use, disclosure, protection and accuracy of personal information collected by Kaitlin Corporation
By using the Kaitlin Corporation web sites, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy and consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information for the purposes set out in this policy. If you do not agree to the Policy, please do not use this site.
We reserve the right, without prior notice, to modify our Privacy Policy as business needs require. We will post any such changes on this web site.
Anyone may visit Kaitlin Corporation web sites without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information.
Kaitlin Corporation collects personal information (shipping address, email address, home telephone number) only when you voluntarily provide it through our online contact forms.
Kaitlin Corporation does not rent or sell your personal information to third parties without your permission.
Our web site may contain links to other web sites that we feel may be of interest or use to you. We do not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content, practices or privacy policies of those sites.
Kaitlin Corporation reserves the right to terminate any user’s access to the web sites at any time, without any liability for damages of any kind.
© KAITLIN CORPORATION 2020
© Copyright 2020. All Rights Reserved.
|
PRIVACY POLICY
Sales centres currently open by appointment only. Please contact us by phone or email to schedule an appointment.
Contact Us
